that I most
that
of us think
I
most
of
us
think
about Earth
about
Earth
But now we're
But
moving into
now
we're
moving
into
space Even data
space
centers think Elon
Even
data
centers
think
Elon
leading that
leading
charge will start
that
charge
will
start
moving into space
moving
into
space
And we won't
And
have the not
we
won't
have
the
not
in my backyard
in
and the bureaucracy
my
backyard
and
the
bureaucracy
associated with
associated
data centers
with
data
centers
There's going to
There's
be huge job
going
to
be
huge
job
creation around the
creation
around
the
space exploration and
space
all of the
exploration
and
all
of
the
opportunities
out there
out
there
And then the
And
other one and
then
the
other
one
and
you'll find this
you'll
in our digital
find
this
in
our
digital
assets section
assets
of Big Ideas
section
of
Big
Ideas
is the digital
is
world private
the
digital
world
private
property rights
property
We know from
rights
We
know
from
economic history the
economic
best way to
history
the
best
way
to
lift people and
lift
countries out
people
and
countries
out
of is with
of
is
with
private property rights
private
that are immutable
property
rights
that
are
immutable
Well that is
Well
now moving into
that
is
now
moving
into
the digital digital
the
world for the
digital
world
for
the
first time thanks
first
to blockchain technology
time
thanks
to
blockchain
technology